<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Archive</title>
    <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Web Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Power BI</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/power-bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/power-bi/</guid>
      <description>Columns vs Measures Calculated columns (and tables) are:
 Evaluated for each row in your table, immediately after you hit &amp;lsquo;Enter&amp;rsquo; to complete the formula Saved back into the model so take up space  Calculated Measures are:
 Evaluated when you use it in a visual, when the visual is rendered Not saved anywhere (well, actually there&amp;rsquo;s a cache in the report layer but it&amp;rsquo;s not part of the file when you hit Save)  Generally, measures are more useful, but the trade-offs are the performance hit (report runtime vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/sql-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/sql-server/</guid>
      <description> Columns vs Measures Figure 3: Organization of teams driven by business capabilities
Figure 3: Organization of teams driven by business capabilities
Add user to Managed Instance
create user DataScienceCore from external provider </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Big Data Overview</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/microsoft-big-data-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/microsoft-big-data-overview/</guid>
      <description>https://academy.microsoft.com/en-us/professional-program/tracks/big-data/
Block 1 – Data Fundamentals Learn data science basics. Explore topics like data queries, data analysis, data visualization and how statistics informs data science practices. Please choose from Course 2a or Course 2b to complete the unit.
 Course 1: Microsoft Professional Program: Introduction to Big Data Course 2a: Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Power BI Course 2b: Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Excel Course 3: Introduction to NoSQL Data Solutions Course 4: Querying Data with Transact-SQL  Unit 2 – Big Data Processing In this unit, you will learn how to use Azure services and open source technologies to implement batch processing and real-time processing of big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging with hugo netlify</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/hugo_netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/hugo_netlify/</guid>
      <description>Here is a great tutorial on how to host hugo on netlify
Create hugo site In order to create a new hugo site simply go:
hugo new site [path] [flags] git Create a new repository on the command line Init the git repo and push it to the guthub repo:
echo &amp;#34;# website2&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; README.md git init git add README.md git commit -m &amp;#34;first commit&amp;#34; git remote add origin https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most useful git commands</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/most-useful-git-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/most-useful-git-commands/</guid>
      <description>Setup Set your details
git config --global user.name &amp;#34;John Doe&amp;#34; git config --global user.email &amp;#34;john@example.com&amp;#34; Use &amp;ndash;global to set the configuration for all projects. If git config is used without &amp;ndash;global and run inside a project directory, the settings are set for the specific project. Make git ignore file modes
cd project/ git config core.filemode false
This option is useful if the file permissions are not important to us, for example when we are on Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCRUM PSM I</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/scrum-psm-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/scrum-psm-i/</guid>
      <description>The complete guido can be downloaded here: scrumguides.org
1. What is Scrum? Scrum is a framework for developing and sustaining complex products. A framework in which complex adaptive problems can be addressed. It is lightweight, simple to understand and yet difficult to master. To simplify, Scrum is not a process or a technique - it is a framework within which you can use different processes and techniques. It has roles, events, artefacts and rules that bind them together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>