<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Web Archive</title>
    <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Web Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Bezos&#39; API Mandate</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/2018-11-20_jeff-bezos-api-mandate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/2018-11-20_jeff-bezos-api-mandate/</guid>
      <description>The best article I&amp;rsquo;ve ever read about architecture and the management of IT.
UPDATE
This post was intended to be shared privately and was accidentally made public. Thanks to +Steve Yegge for allowing us to keep it out there. It&amp;rsquo;s the sort of writing people do when they think nobody is watching: honest, clear, and frank.
The world would be a better place if more people wrote this sort of internal memoranda, and even better if they were allowed to write it for the outside world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data Initiative</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/brookes-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/brookes-law/</guid>
      <description>In a Field Notes post from 2014, LeadingAgile consultant Andrew Fuqua considers Brooks’ Law in the context of the Theory of Constraints.
 Brooks’ Law is the adage that adding manpower to a late software project makes it later.
 Fuqua notes that Brooks observed people “and months are interchangeable commodities only when a task can be partitioned among many workers with no communication among them.”
Effective communication is key to any project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data Initiative</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/open-data-initiative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/open-data-initiative/</guid>
      <description>A groundbreaking partnership with a new vision for renewable data and intelligent applications Digital transformation is how you compete and win today. It’s the path to better serve customers, build better products, and empower employees. And it&amp;rsquo;s data that is the foundational resource that allows you to transform and uncover the insights you need to drive business forward.
Adobe, Microsoft, and SAP are partnering on the Open Data Initiative to enable data to be exchanged—and enriched—across systems, making it a renewable resource that flows into intelligent applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conway&#39;s Law</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/conways-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/conways-law/</guid>
      <description>Many organizations have become adept at identifying what they need from software development projects, based on a keen understanding of their business goals. Even so, they’re often surprised to find out that the end results don’t achieve the transformative impact they were expecting. Their mistake? Overlooking the importance of Conway’s Law.
In 1967, Melvin Conway coined a phrase at the end of his publication ‘How do committees invent?’ that was subsequently made popular by Fred Brooks in his book The Mythical Man-Month, where he dubbed it &amp;lsquo;Conway’s Law&amp;rsquo;, which states:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>