<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Web Archive</title>
    <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Web Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Power BI</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/power-bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/power-bi/</guid>
      <description>Columns vs Measures Calculated columns (and tables) are:
 Evaluated for each row in your table, immediately after you hit &amp;lsquo;Enter&amp;rsquo; to complete the formula Saved back into the model so take up space  Calculated Measures are:
 Evaluated when you use it in a visual, when the visual is rendered Not saved anywhere (well, actually there&amp;rsquo;s a cache in the report layer but it&amp;rsquo;s not part of the file when you hit Save)  Generally, measures are more useful, but the trade-offs are the performance hit (report runtime vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/sql-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/sql-server/</guid>
      <description>Actual Execution Plan Figure 3: Organization of teams driven by business capabilities
Figure 3: Organization of teams driven by business capabilities
Add user to Managed Instance create user DataScienceCore from external provider There are two types of Indexes in SQL Server:
 Clustered Index Non-Clustered Index  Clustered Index A clustered index defines the order in which data is physically stored in a table. Table data can be sorted in only way, therefore, there can be only one clustered index per table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Big Data Overview</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/microsoft-big-data-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/microsoft-big-data-overview/</guid>
      <description>https://academy.microsoft.com/en-us/professional-program/tracks/big-data/
Block 1 – Data Fundamentals Learn data science basics. Explore topics like data queries, data analysis, data visualization and how statistics informs data science practices. Please choose from Course 2a or Course 2b to complete the unit.
 Course 1: Microsoft Professional Program: Introduction to Big Data Course 2a: Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Power BI Course 2b: Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Excel Course 3: Introduction to NoSQL Data Solutions Course 4: Querying Data with Transact-SQL  Unit 2 – Big Data Processing In this unit, you will learn how to use Azure services and open source technologies to implement batch processing and real-time processing of big data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Basics</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/docker-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/docker-basics/</guid>
      <description>Docker is a tool which helps developers build and ship high quality applications, faster, anywhere. Source
Why Docker With Docker, developers can build any app in any language using any toolchain. Dockerized apps are completely portable and can run anywhere.
Developers can get going by just spinning any container out of list on Docker Hub. Docker manages and tracks changes and dependencies, making it easier for sysadmins to understand how the apps that developers build work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Fultz&#39; grpc package</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/grpc-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/grpc-package/</guid>
      <description>Instructions Link to instructions
git clone https://github.com/grpc/grpc.git grpc.git cd grpc.git/ # git checkout tags/release-0_11_1 # does not exist Now we have to initialize the submodules and this is where it becomes tricky:
git submodule update --init cd third_party/protobuf/ ./autogen.sh  Google changed some of its internal structures and now gmock is part of google test. Anyways, the URL in the autpgen.sh is not working anymore. There we need to manually extract gmock into protobuf:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most useful git commands</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/most-useful-git-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/most-useful-git-commands/</guid>
      <description>Setup Set your details
git config --global user.name &amp;#34;John Doe&amp;#34; git config --global user.email &amp;#34;john@example.com&amp;#34; Use --global to set the configuration for all projects. If git config is used without --global and run inside a project directory, the settings are set for the specific project.
Make git ignore file modes
cd project/ git config core.filemode false This option is useful if the file permissions are not important to us, for example when we are on Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum PSM I</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/scrum-psm-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/scrum-psm-i/</guid>
      <description>After getting scrum.org the PSM I I wanted to capture the relevant content.
The complete guido can be downloaded here: scrumguides.org
1. What is Scrum? Scrum is a framework for developing and sustaining complex products. A framework in which complex adaptive problems can be addressed. It is lightweight, simple to understand and yet difficult to master. To simplify, Scrum is not a process or a technique - it is a framework within which you can use different processes and techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>