<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Learning on Web Archive</title>
    <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine Learning on Web Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Linear Regression</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/machine-learning/2018-01_linear_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/machine-learning/2018-01_linear_regression/</guid>
      <description>Source https://www.analyticsvidhya.com/blog/2017/09/common-machine-learning-algorithms/
It is used to estimate real values (cost of houses, number of calls, total sales etc.) based on continuous variable(s). Here, we establish relationship between independent and dependent variables by fitting a best line. This best fit line is known as regression line and represented by a linear equation
$$Y= a *X + b$$
The best way to understand linear regression is to relive this experience of childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logistic Regression</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/machine-learning/2018-02_logistic_regression/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/machine-learning/2018-02_logistic_regression/</guid>
      <description>Don’t get confused by its name! It is a classification not a regression algorithm. It is used to estimate discrete values (binary values like 0/1, yes/no, true/false ) based on given set of independent variable(s). In simple words, it predicts the probability of occurrence of an event by fitting data to a logit function. Hence, it is also known as logit regression. Since, it predicts the probability, its output values lies between 0 and 1 (as expected).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Overview</title>
      <link>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/machine-learning/2018-01_machine_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://elastic-fermat-3dc26c.netlify.com/machine-learning/2018-01_machine_learning/</guid>
      <description>Broadly, there are three types of Machine Learning Algorithms..
1. Supervised Learning How it works: This algorithm consist of a target or outcome variable (or dependent variable) which is to be predicted from a given set of predictors (independent variables). Using these set of variables, we generate a function that map inputs to desired outputs. The training process continues until the model achieves a desired level of accuracy on the training data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>