<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Visualization on Web Archive</title>
    <link>https://data-analytics.netlify.com/tags/visualization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Visualization on Web Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://data-analytics.netlify.com/tags/visualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Power BI</title>
      <link>https://data-analytics.netlify.com/power-bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://data-analytics.netlify.com/power-bi/</guid>
      <description>Columns vs Measures Calculated columns (and tables) are:
 Evaluated for each row in your table, immediately after you hit &amp;lsquo;Enter&amp;rsquo; to complete the formula Saved back into the model so take up space  Calculated Measures are:
 Evaluated when you use it in a visual, when the visual is rendered Not saved anywhere (well, actually there&amp;rsquo;s a cache in the report layer but it&amp;rsquo;s not part of the file when you hit Save)  Generally, measures are more useful, but the trade-offs are the performance hit (report runtime vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Server</title>
      <link>https://data-analytics.netlify.com/sql-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://data-analytics.netlify.com/sql-server/</guid>
      <description>Columnstore A columnstore index can provide a very high level of data compression, typically by 10 times, to significantly reduce your data warehouse storage cost. For analytics, a columnstore index offers an order of magnitude better performance than a btree index. Columnstore indexes are the preferred data storage format for data warehousing and analytics workloads. Starting with SQL Server 2016 (13.x), you can use columnstore indexes for real-time analytics on your operational workload.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>